frogfaucet.com 2016-06-01

# Privacy policy | FrogFaucet - free bitcoin faucet!

FrogFaucet.com Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.   

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address, Bitcoin Address or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you While Playing the game or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

      **•** To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 

We do not use an SSL certificate 

      **•** We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information 

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**We use cookies to:**

      **•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.   

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

However, you can still place orders . 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**     
www.frogfaucet.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**     
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.frogfaucet.com.    
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.frogfaucet.com and other sites on the Internet.     
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....    
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.frogfaucet.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  

www.frogfaucet.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.frogfaucet's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.  

**Log Files**   
Like many other Web sites, www.frogfaucet.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. 

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

** We have implemented the following: **

      **•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting 

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

Opting out:   
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf   

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously 

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. 

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: 

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page 

Users are able to change their personal information: 

      **•** By emailing us 

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking 

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We will notify the users via in site notification 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.frogfaucet.com   
  
* * *

Using cryptocurrency in online - gambling, demonstrating their ability to gambling To begin, consider what is an online gambling (gambling - gambling or gaming organization). with the advent of computer network on the Internet, there is such kind of services like online - casino. The first such casino was opened in 1997 in the United States. There was created the opportunity to play the same games of chance, as in the conventional gaming establishments. At the request of the players were there and poker, and blackjack, roulette, and not to mention about the gaming machines (video poker and video slot). Over time, at the online gambling market appeared company who develop this business: Microgaming, Playtech, Igrosoft, Novomatic, Onlyplay and many others. Online - gambling refers to a sufficiently large and profitable business. As early as 2012, studies were conducted Gambling Capital, showed that the annual turnover in the online environment - gambling totaled 28.5 billion dollars. Today the company Gambling Compliance which monitors global gaming industry, believes that the real value of online – gaming only in the US ranges from 4 to 7 billion. Well, this proves that the gambling industry in the network is already well developed, but it is a percentage of the total gambling is not more than 10%. And there is space for development, and hope for rapid progress gives cryptocurrency attraction.  
What is most  needed  for organizers online casinos and their customers? Players worry about comfort of organized games and own anonymity. And organizers of care and guarantee timely payment. traditional calculations create problems for the organizers and players, and it is prolonged in time, the timing of payments and extremely high interest rates. Namely cryptocurrency, the best way to meet these requirements, if it is specially created for this purpose. What are the advantages of Bitcoin fiat currency in the online - gambling? First of all, it Bitcoins decentralized and its independence from the government and any other agencies. The important role played by the fact that traditional fiat calculations provide players some problems. This and terms of payment of winnings, is often prolonged in time, not to mention the extremely high commission percentage. As we have already mentioned above, there is also the problem of anonymous players who are worried about their privacy and the confidentiality of their remittances.  
Bitcoin and other cryptocurrency able to solve these problems. The laws of countries do not apply to it and do not prohibit online - gambling. They provide almost instant transfer of funds from one Bitcoin - wallet to another, anywhere in the world, providing complete transparency of transactions. Note that the rate paid can not be returned back. A fee is a very small percentage. Yes, Bitcoin and other cryptocurrency not guarantee complete anonymity, but using such new developments as Darkcoin and Cryptonote, the ability to identify an extremely reduced.  
Gambling existed on the entire interval of civilization. The modern world has provided an opportunity to dive into the world of their own interests with the help of a computer, making bets using Bitcoins or other cryptocurrency. But recall that the term "gambling" also means a gaming addiction, which destroyed not one human life.

* * *

First of all we need to understand what these terms mean. The term "cryptocurrency" is a direct translation of the English term «cryptocurrency, which means that electronic money protected by encoding. What functions designed to perform cryptocurrency? In today's world, a huge segment of business would be impossible without the so-called digital or electronic money. Because they allow you to pay for goods bought on the Internet, and not only.  Cryptocurrency  system one of the fastest and most reliable payment systems and remittances. Add to this that cryptocurrency not tied to banking institutions and are not controlled by government organizations around the world.  
About value and essence of the term "cryptocurrency" more clear. Now pay attention to the most famous representative cryptocurrency - Bitcoin. He takes his foundation as well as the term "cryptocurrency» from English. «Bit» is the smallest unit of information, and the «coin» - coin. Bitcoin is also recorded in the transcription - BTC. This reduction is popular among the authors who write on economic issues and on the stock exchange. The term "Bitcoin" is inseparable from the concept of cryptocurrency because he was the first, and became the most famous in the world.  
Now look at Bitcoin as currency. First of all it is a digital product with limited supply, and the low offer due to the fact that his algorithm is structured so that the network can function only Bitcoin 21 million coins. Currently, the BTC produced 14815675. And after the "Miner" obtain the last bitcoin, their numbers remain unchanged. Schedule of emissions registered in the program and is known in advance. The economic basis bitcoin based on deflationary model, and it causes some concern to economists. They doubt whether this will be enough of a relatively small number of coins for everyday calculations. Although 1 Bitcoin is divided into 100,000,000 particles, which in honor of the founder of Bitcoin, called "Satoshi", and this makes it possible to operate with almost unlimited volumes of cryptocurrency. Also referred to as "millibitcoin" and microbitcoin "- is one thousandth and one millionth of Bitcoins, respectively.  
31 October 2008, with the publication of a fundamental document, began to develop the concept of Bitcoin. Published this person working under the pseudonym Satoshi Nakamoto. Interestingly, in spite of numerous journalistic investigations, until today failed to find the real creator of Bitcoin.  
And on January 3, 2009, at 18:45 GMT, the network was generated by the first unit, it was the so-called "Genesis" - the block. And on this day all over the world celebrate the birthday of Bitcoin.

* * *

Is it possible to earn from the hobby? Of course. Everyone can receive profit from his or her favorite work. If you make this during your free from main work time, you won’t earn big funds, however, you can enable a quite pleasant addition to your primary income. Someone twines wreathes of vine and sells them, someone collects ancient coins or rare notes, which is a long-term investment, someone paints, sings, or makes cool sailing ship models – this all can bring a good income. Someone would regret having a hobby and say that his or her free time is passed by surfing the world network.

So let’s talk about the last variant. Surfing the global network can also help you to receive additional earnings. If you practice it at your free from the main work time, then you won’t earn much, however, you will have some additional income. The websites that offer free Bitcoins will help us with that.

What is Bitcoin? This is a kind of digital currency (other name – crypto-currency), which has a high level of security and is widely used within the network. Quite many Internet-markets exist that sell their goods or services for Bitcoins. This crypto-currency slowly gains the status of the network gold, because it demonstrates great stability so far. Another crypto-currencies exist as well, but Bitcoin was the first one, the most people heard about it, it has the highest rate, which is 420$/BTC, and the biggest capitalization.

So how can you receive Bitcoin for free? There are specific websites that are called Bitcoin faucets, and they offer such a possibility. Such strange name was gained because these websites give crypto-currency by very small portions, but regularly like water drops from the faucet. The fact that you have to visit Bitcoin faucets regularly, makes the sense of their functioning, since their income is received from the ads placed on these websites. That is why you should deactivate the ad block programs when you visit Bitcoin faucets (well, most websites just won’t let you in, if the ad blocker is on).

In addition, you have to create a Bitcoin wallet. This is easy to do, network has a plenty of guides how to do this. When you visit a website with the faucet, you have to enter the Bitcoin wallet address in the corresponding field, enter a captcha, and wait until you get free Bitcoin. Of course, this sum is not big, but this procedure can be repeated regularly, and you can visit several faucets, they are really multiple in the network. So if you pass your free time on the Internet, why not monetize your Internet-surfing and get wants and needs meet.
